LEO MAHLANGU, IT Intern

10671 Lurie Avenue. Benoni, 1520, Gauteng

Software Engineer/Developer



PROFILE

A goal-oriented, well-structured person with a keen interest and skill in Information Technology. Currently completed studies at Richfield Graduate Institute of Technology studying a Bachelor of Sciences in Information Technology degree specializing in Emerging Technologies. Possesses a diverse set of talents in networking and computer languages, therefore being an invaluable asset to any organization.

OBJECTIVE

To lead a team of diverse professionals in creating and maintaining effective, efficient, life-changing and problem-solving software.

QUALIFICATIONS

Richfield Graduate Institute of Technology/Current Honours in Information Technology (Candidate)

Richfield Graduate Institute of Technology / Dec 2023 Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

University of Johannesburg / Dec 2023 Certificate in Artificial Intelligence (Short Course)

AWS Academy Graduate / Dec 2023

Tel: 067 136 0257 • E-mail:

mailto:leothokozanimahlangu@gmail.com

SKILLS

- Java
- SQL
- Python
- VB.Net
- HTML
- C++
- PHP
- CSS
- Mobile Application Development
- Website Development
- Cloud Computing
- AWS Core Services
- AWS Pricing
- AWS Support
- AWS Web Services
- AWS Cloud
- AWS Architecture
- JavaScript eXtension (JSX)
- JSON
- Wireless Networking
- JavaScript
- Front-end Development.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Information Technology Intern, Netsurit Nov 2023 – Present

Provision of third-party support services.

Responsibilities include but are not limited to:

- Remotely assisting clients with technical issues.
- Escalating/allocating calls to the correct people.

IT Technician (Volunteer), Global Top Int Aug 2023 – Oct 2023

Responsible for maintaining the good health of computer hardware and software. My responsibilities include:

- Installing required software
- Updating existing software

Vacation Work Student, Vodacom Group Limited Jul 2023 – Jul 2023

Assisting staff with the development of new and updated software. Responsibilities included:

- Completing daily tasks using the company's software.
- Conducting research.
- Front-end and back-end development.
- Presentations.

SOFTWARES

Microsoft Android Studio Visual Studio GitHub VS Code XAMPP Classification: UNCLASSIFIED

ACHIEVEMENTS

• Completed my qualification (Bachelor of Science in Information Technology) with distinction.

REFERENCES

Teddy Shabani Director Global Top Int South Africa Mobile: 072 200

South Africa Mobile: 072 209 8969

E-mail: mbledlatbhitea

Dzivhu Mavhungu Learning Project Manager Vodacom Group Limited Mobile: 082 330 2000

E-mail: mailto:: Dzivhu.mavhungu@vodacom.co.za

Sibongile Masego 3rd Party Team Leader Netsurit

Mobile: 011 555 7000

E-mail: mailto:SibongileM@netsurit.com